Guide to the James A. Roberts Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-290
  - Broadstone III Specific Plan DEIR 11/1990 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Broadstone III Specific Plan EIR proposal 3/1991 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Broadstone III Specific Plan EIR 3/1991 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Broadstone I Water Quality Management Plan 5/1991 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - EDCWA FEIR 3/1993 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous articles, papers (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Iceland/Denmark Sacramento visit 10/1991 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Roberts Iceland working notes 11/1991 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - EIA visits 9-10/1991 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - AEP CEQA Workshop 1995 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Marcel Pardo (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Coastal Management handbook 1960 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Charles Knapp (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - California Permit Handbook 1994 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Deskbook 1995 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - City of Folsom General Plan Update 11/1987 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Alaska Petroleum Contractors Inc. 1996 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Folsom Billing Information (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Russell Ranch Specific Plan EIR Responses 7/1992 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - EAFP/Russell Ranch EIR comments (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Russell Ranch Specific Plan EIR vol.2 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Russell Ranch Specific Plan EIR vol.3&4 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Willow Creek Specific Plan EIR 1/1991 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - EIR examples, Sonoma (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Nevada County General Plan 1980-1990 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - EIR examples: Pacific Texas Pipeline 1985; Lower American River Streambank Protection 1996; Celeron/All American & Getty Pipelines 1984; California Spotted Owl Management 1995 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - NAFTA v.1&2 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Department of Energy Office of Technology Management reports 6/1995 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - MCP Preliminary Arborist’s Reports (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - MCP Preliminary Arborist’s Reports (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - MCP DEIR vol.1 11/1989 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - EIR examples: Santa Rosa Wastewater Management Plan DEIR 1986; Sacramento Federal Building 1994; Sacramento Submerged Cultural Resources Survey/Archeological Investigation 1986 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous reports (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Russell Ranch correspondence (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Russell Ranch EIR, reports (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - EIR examples: Willow Creek Estates South 1986; American River Watershed, Bridge Crossing; Alder Creek 1985-1992; Sante Fe Center 1988 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - EIR example: Prairie City Center 1992 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Tahoe National Forest EIS 1990 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - El Dorado National forest Land & Resource Management Plan 1988 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Sweden B1 1988 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Sweden B3 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Sweden B4 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Sweden B4 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Project Workbench software, floppy discs (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Air Quality publications (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Risk publications (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Chevron Health Risk Assessment 1996 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Chevron Risk Management & Prevention Plan (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - 05792 Chevron Preliminary ADEIR 3/1993 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Chevron- ARCO Los Angeles Refinery EIR CFP 1993 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - California Department of Corrections Proposal Conference Vol.1 of 2 1995 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - EIR examples: EAFP 1990, Russell Ranch 1987; Silverbrook 1992; Marlboro Square 1988; Blue Ravine 1989-1992; Folsom-Intel 1988-1992; Folsom Historical District 1989; Natoma Station 1989; Lancaster Landfill 1990; Antelope Valley 1991 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Monitored Retrievable Storage Facility Screening & Evaluation Report Vol.1-3 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Sweden miscellaneous 1990 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - SSC Environmental Setting Report 1988 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - SSC Stockton Site Proposal 1987 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - SWRCB California Inland Surface Water Plan 1991 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Coastal Project Photomontage Proposal (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - U.S.-Mexico Border Governors Finance Summit 1989 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Sacramento Central City Community Plan (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Roberts Working Notes CEQA audit (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - APA Publications 1990-1993 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - EIR examples: B&J Landfill 1993; Grace Chemicals; Keller Canyon Landfill 1990 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - EIR examples: Silverbrook 1991-1992; Santa Fe Center 1988; Prairie City Center 1992; Briggs Ranch 1989; Folsom Auto Plaza 1985; Natomas West Assessment District 1988; NE Roseville Specific Plan 1986; Sonoma Roblar Road Quarry; Sonoma Landfill Sears Point 1989; El Dorado Irrigation District 1991-1993; Russell Ranch 1991; Nevada County Business Park 1986-1987 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - EIR examples: Sherwin Ski Area; Lower Laguna Drainage Study 1992, Glenshire Waddle 1972; Santa Barbara Desalination 1991 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - SHPRC meeting 10/25/1996 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Roberts Iceland presentation 5/7/1991 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Powerline IA: contract (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Roberts “Tradewins” 3/5/1996 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - 601 1988-1989 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Powerline 1a: General correspondence (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, Iceland publications (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - NEPA workshop 11/1993 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - EIA course: Iceland 01391 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - NHPRC Guidelines (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Royston, Hanamoto, Alley & Abbey/GEMS F3 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Boverket contract 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Sweden work 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Hawaii Geothermal Project Pele Defense Fund 1991 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Hawaii Geothermal Project Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund 1990 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Roberts Folsom City Environmental Monitoring Paper Draft (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Kenya Methodist University (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Sweden B5 1990 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Sweden B5 1990 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - MCP ADEIR 1989 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - MCP EIR v.1 Appendices A-F 1989 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - MCP EIR v.1 Appendices G-H (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - EIR examples: Alder Creek Auto Center 1992; Yosemite Valley Housing Plan 1992; El Dorado National Forest; Yosemite Concession Services Plan 1992; Tahoe National Forest; Mount Shasta Ski Area (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - EIR examples: California Spotted Owl; Sierra Nevada; El Dorado National Forest Cleveland Fire Area Recovery 1993; UCSB 1990; Russell Ranch Specific Plan 1991; Bureau of Reclamation Interior Water Acquisition 1995 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - MCP Preliminary Arborist’s Reports (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - MCP Preliminary Arborist’s Reports (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Coastal Management reports 1977-1993 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - EAFP Draft Comment Responses (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - EAFP Plan (Spink) 1990 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - EAFP Technical Report, Descriptive document (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - EAFP DEIR v.1 1990 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Natoma Station DEIR 1989 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Marlboro Square Development Project 1987 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Parkway Development Blue Ravine 1992 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Silverbrook DEIR 1991 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - American River Crossing Project EIR Responses (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Sonoma County General Plan 1986 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Broadstone Master Plan DEIR, FEIR 1990-1991 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Broadstone III Specific Plan ADEIR 1992 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Auburn Indian Hills Project DEIR 1985 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Auburn Indian Hills FEIR Supplement 1986 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Natomas West Improvement DEIR 1990 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Natomas Ditch Replacement 1989 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Joerger Ranch EIR 1972 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Santa Fe Center DEIR & Comment Responses (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Silverbrook Specific Plan DEIR 1991 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Silverbrook Specific Plan FEIR 1992 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Silverbrook Specific Plan Design Guidelines 1991 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Antelope Valley Landfill DEIR 1991 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Contra Costa County Solid Waste FEIR Amendments Responses 1989 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - East Contra Costa Landfill DEIR 1986 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - East Contra Costa Landfill FEIR Responses 1987 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Briggs Ranch Residential Development FEIR 1989 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Briggs Ranch Mitigation Monitoring 1989 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Briggs Ranch ADEIR 1989 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Briggs Ranch DEIR (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - EAFP EIR Binder 3 of 5 1991-92 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - EAFP Final DEIR Binder 4 of 5 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - EAFP Comments (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - California Mining Newsletters 1990 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - California Mining Association Reclamation (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - California Mining Association Air Quality (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Folsom P.C. Recommendations on EIR, General Plan Amendments, EAFP Summary Binder 1992 (Box 150, Folder 1)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2001-226
  - Sweden Environmental Management Summit (EMS) Correspondence 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sweden EMS: Budget Ideas (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sweden EMS: Cancellation/Refund Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sweden EMS: To-Dos (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sweden EMS: General Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sweden EMS: IIIEEE (International Institute for Industrial Environmental Economics) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sweden General (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sweden EMS: WELF (World Environmental Law Foundation) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sweden EMS: Fact sheets (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sweden EMS: general, through 1/20/1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sweden 10/1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sweden publications (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sweden EMS: Correspondence 8/1999-5/2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sweden EMS: information requests (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sweden EMS: Participants (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sweden EMS: Ronneby (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sweden EMS: Announcements (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sweden EMS: INEM (International Network for Environmental Management) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sweden MoDo/Sydkraft publications (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - McKenna & Cuneo 10/1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Office of Technology Policy, other publications (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Roberts photographs & negatives (Boy’s Soccer Team) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EIR examples, 1998: Sierra Nevada Forest Service; Central Valley Improvement Act; American River Slurry Wall; EDCWA; El Dorado National Forest Grazing Strategy (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous articles & newsletters (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - California Department of Parks and Recreation Preliminary Environmental Assessment, Roberts Budget Change Proposal (COBCP) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - California Department of Parks and Recreation Indian Museum COBCP & related (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 4082 CVP (Central Valley Project) 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 4082 CVP 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 4082 CVP 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 4082 El Dorado County Water Services 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 4082.00.200 97010 EDCWA/CVP Project Contacts (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 4082 CVP (3) 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 4082.00.100 97010 EDCWA/CVP Contracts (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 4082 CVP (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 4082 CVP (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - EDCWA STAC Book 4 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - EDCWA Board 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Plan (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - EDCWA STAC Book 3 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - EDCWA EIP Bills/Task Orders #2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - EDCWA EIP Bills/Task Orders #2 cont. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - EDCWA Bureau Accounting (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - EDCWA TAC Steering Committee 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - EDCWA EIP Bills/Task Orders #1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - EDCWA STAC meetings to 3/2000 Book 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - EDCWA Board Meeting Minutes & Agendas 1988-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - EDCWA PG&E Divestiture (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mokelumne Wilderness reports and related (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service Sierra Nevada Foothills Region 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CALFED (California-Federal) Water project reports, Bay-Delta program 1999 Watershed, Water Quality, Water Use, etc. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CALFED reports, Bay-Delta program- Watershed, Water Quality, Water Use, etc. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Status of the Sierra Nevada Report 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CVP Supplemental EIS 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Calfed Bay-Delta memoranda and reports (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Calfed Bay-Delta Reports 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Calfed Bay-Delta (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Calfed Bay-Delta EIR (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Calfed Bay-Delta memoranda, meeting agenda (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - SEC (Sacramento Environmental Commission) Correspondence, reports, memoranda 1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - SEC Mather Airport Land Use Plan 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - SEC Keifer Landfill reports 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - SEC Nature Conservancy (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - SEC Correspondence, memoranda, etc. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - SEC Roberts Book 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - SEC Roberts Book 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SEC Roberts Book 3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SEC 4/24/2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SEC 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SEC Hirsch (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - SEC publications, newsletters, reports, EIR (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - SEC California Historic Preservation Commission & State Records Advisory Board (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SEC Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Taiwan Miscellaneous memoranda, Correspondence 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Taiwan trip 3/1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Taiwan Phase II Proposal materials (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Taiwan post-March Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Taiwan reports and related (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Taiwan Miscellaneous Roberts personal (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Taiwan publications (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Taiwan Water Resources (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Taiwan reports, publications (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Taiwan publications- Sustainability, National Parks, Travel & Tourism, etc. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan Roberts report and correspondence (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sweden Varberg 2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sweden Goteberg (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sweden Stockholm (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sweden Environmental Advisory Council (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Sweden NRC (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sweden travel publications (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sweden Svenska Miljostyrningsvadet (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sweden Ministry of Environment Indicators (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sweden Ministry of Environment publications (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sweden Volvo Environmental Management (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Sweden Boverket (National Board of Housing Building & Planning) publications (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Sweden Boverket publications, etc. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sweden publications (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sweden INEM reports (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sweden Alnarp publications (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Sweden Syfkraft publications (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sweden publications (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sweden Hollandsas (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sweden Jokkmokk (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sweden Boverket reports (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sweden SAS, other corporation reports (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sweden trip 6-7/2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sweden Boverket publications (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan reports 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan maps, guidebooks, etc. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Taiwan travel guides, brochures, maps, etc. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Yosemite Valley Plan 11/2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Yosemite Valley Plan 11/2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Sierra Nevada Forest Plan Amendment EIS (4 of 6 v.) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - MMA China Coal Project background reports (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - MMA Environmental & Social Impact Audit 2/2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - MMA Environmental & Social Impact Audit 1/2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - MMA Pre-Feasibility Study 8/1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - MMA correspondence, memoranda (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - MMA IFC Environmental Division (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MMA Marshall Miller & Associates (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - MMA Topographical maps (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - MMA Administration (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - MMA Public consultation (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - MMA Traffic (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - MMA Handbooks & Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - MMA Technical Reports (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - MMA Photographs, negatives, CD-Rs (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - MMA Correspondence, memoranda 5/2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - MMA Correspondence, memoranda, articles 1-3/2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - MMA “Danang Coal Project” Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - MMA Correspondence, reports, 5/2000-5/2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - MMA publications, maps, brochures, magazines, postcards (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - MMA Correspondence, memoranda 5/2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - MMA viewgraphs 4/2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - MMA Community Development Strategy 5/2/2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - MMA Environmental & Social Impact Audit 3/2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - EDCWA ESA (Endangered Species Act) lawsuits (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - EDCWA ESA reports, Correspondence California Red Legged Frog, etc. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - EDCWA ESA California Red Legged Frog Draft Recovery Plan 1/2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - EDCWA ESA California Red Legged Frog Restoration Plan & related 8/2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - EDCWA ESA Frogs (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - EDCWA ESA California Spotted Owl, Yosemite Toad & Mountain Yellow Legged Frog Petitions & related (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - EDCWA Supreme Court Ruling re: Wetlands 1/2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - EDCWA Calfed Bay-Delta Program reports, memoranda 7-8/2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - EDCWA El Dorado Hydroelectric (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - EDCWA CEQA (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - EDCWA CVP reports 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - EDCWA CVP Draft Biological Opinion (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - EDCWA NFS Land Resource Management Final Rule 11/2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - EDCWA Calfed Bay-Delta report, Correspondence, memoranda (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Forest Plan Amendment Project DEIS map packet 11/2000 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Forest Plan Amendment Project EIS Record of Decision (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Forest Plan Amendment Project DEIS v.1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Forest Plan Amendment Project DEIS v.2-3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Forest Plan Amendment Project Forest Service Employees for Environmental Ethics “Restoring Our Forest Legacy” 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Forest Plan Amendment Project Forest Service Roadless Area Conservation DEIS v.1&2 5/2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - EDCWA NPS Merced Wild & Scenic River EIS (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - EDCWA CVP EIP (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - EDCWA Cumulative & Interagency Coordination (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - EDCWA Amador County & Sierra Club (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - EDCWA Placer County Water Agency (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - EDCWA Water Forum & related (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - EDCWA EIP Spring Survey 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - EDCWA Sierra Nevada Framework (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - EDCWA Water Availability Needs Assessment (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - EDCWA Special Studies- Calfed, CVP 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - EDCWA 97010 Roberts Working file (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - EDCWA Habitat Conservation Plan (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - EDCWA Sacramento County Habitat Conservation Plan (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - EDCWA EIP Statement of Qualification (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - EDCWA EIP Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - EDCWA U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - EDCWA Project Description Draft (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - SJUSD (San Juan Unified School District) Measure “S” Oversight Committee 1/1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - SJUSD meeting agenda, Correspondence 8/2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - SJUSD Facilities Improvement Program 7/2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - SJUSD meeting agendas, progress reports, Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 5-8/2000 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 3-5/2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Roberts chronological, NAEP Correspondence 8/1999-5/2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Roberts chronological, NAEP Correspondence 5-6/2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Roberts chronological, NAEP Correspondence 8-9/2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Roberts chronological, NAEP Correspondence 5-9/2000 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 3-4/2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Roberts chronological, NAEP Correspondence 11/1999-1/2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 11/1999-2/2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous publications- NAEP News, etc. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 7/1999-11/1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 6-7/2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 2-4/1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 6-9/1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - NHPRC San Diego Historical Society evaluation 10/1999 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 9-10/1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 5-6/1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Roberts chronological, NAEP Correspondence 11-12/2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 11-12/2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - SHPRC (State Historic Preservation Commission) 1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - CHPRC 12/1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - SHPRC memoranda, Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - ICL (Institute for Conservation Leadership) 1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - ICL meeting 9/1998 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Sierra Conservation Center Effluent Disposal Pipeline (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 1-4/2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - AEP/CALNAEP conference 2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - NAEP Conference Materials 5/2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jubilee 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Roberts Family Photographs 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)